Bam, how you doing? So, finally, we are
here in order to be able to show you the
product I've been saying on my channel
for a little while from the kind folks
at Spooky2. Now, because we are
spiritual on this channel and we do a
lot of meditating, we do a lot of aura
healing,
chakra healing, negative thinking, this
machine is classed as basically your
soulmate.
Through this channel, we obviously deal
with frequencies and what we feel
empathically
from our soulmates and from our
soul groups of people that when we're
going through our karma, things can get
very difficult and our auras can be
blocked and we can feel a lot of
blockages and a lot of negative thinking
and we go through a lot of stuff when
we're spiritual but when we're human in
general, right? So, the kind folks at
Spooky2 have sent over this product for
me to review and they've also given me
quite a bit of time in order to be able
to do it because of my unfortunate
accident I did predict of when I hit a
deer and I've had to buy a new car and
everything else but they have been so
kind to me by giving me extra time in
order to review it and actually test out
the product.
So, after this part of where I show you
what you get with the beginners
package, okay, and there will also be a
link provided below for you that will
give you offer I think it's 4 or 5% not
really sure it's one or the other. Think
it's 5% but it will be a discount code
that is below this video, okay,
that you can click on and you can go
over to the site and take a look. It
will more than likely be where you have
to put in the discount code and they
will give you a discount on your product
and what you buy. You can actually buy
individual pieces, you don't have to
like buy the whole set because there are
different packages and different sets of
what you can buy. But if you've already
got one because a lot of you have been
telling me that you have dealt with like
rife machines cuz it's what it is it's a
rife machine
in the past, if you do already have
Spooky2 products, great.
Cuz then you can use the product code
below in order to be able to maybe buy
yourself another piece of equipment that
you can add on to this. That is the
great thing about this is that with the
beginners package that you buy,
it's not ended. There are so much more
things that you can add on to it. And
what I would like to also say is that
for many of you that may be looking at
healing a job or you do do jobs in like
massage therapy or therapy itself or
beauty therapy even, you can add these
kind of products into what you offer
clients spiritually as well. Like if you
have a shop, a spiritual shop or
anything like that, this is very good
that you can actually start to earn some
money by doing so, okay, by adding into
what you offer with your beauty therapy,
nails even and stuff like that, what you
know, whatever you goes do, you? Okay,
all men.
Um
So, let's start off with very generally
of what we get because unfortunately I
was so eager to get it going that I've
thrown away all of the packaging so I
can't really do an unboxing. But I will
show you individually what the products
are. So, obviously we've got the two
channel signal generator from Spooky2
and basically you have to plug it into
your PC,
okay. Um
And then obviously one into a power
outlet, okay?
You do have to have, don't quote me on
this but I'm sure I am right, is is that
you have to use Windows. So, it has to
be a Windows PC,
okay? I do not think that this runs on
Mac. I'm not sure if they run on any
kind of like pad
but it would not be able to but it would
not be a iPad because that is obviously
Mac. So, I'm not sure if they've worked
a way around that but as far as I know,
you would have to have something that's
running Windows, okay? Because you also
get a program and after this part this
section is where the interesting bit is
and you're going to want to see that bit
because I've put together a a spiritual
package for us of what I feel would be
very good for a morning routine in order
for us to go over every time that we
wake up. I mean, I've been using this
and I do remote viewing as you know and
I do a lot of channeling and remote
viewing. I don't really do so many much
tarot cards anymore.
But this has helped with my remote
viewing and channeling and having a very
good connection with spirit and myself,
which is spirit.
Are you channeling yourself? But it's
it's very good for those kind of things
to open you up and keep you cleansed and
clear in order to be able to start off
your day to see if it helps your
visions, to unblock you and to continue
on with your spiritual journey, okay,
especially if you do spiritual work
with tarot card readings and clients and
stuff.
So, generally what we get is the Spooky2
two signal generator, okay? Now, with
the power of editing,
we have a clean table. So,
I thought I would do it individually
instead of creating such chaos on my
table here.
So, this is the box that Spooky2 sends
you and it has everything inside and
there is so much in here that it's like
Christmas, pretty much. It's like
opening up multiple different presents
all at once in one box, okay? So, when
you open up your box, you're going to be
surprised on how much stuff is actually
in here that you can use to get you
started, okay? So, I'm going to I'm
going to go through each individual
thing that we've kind of got. We've
definitely got that I've just gone over
which is the generator, okay, that can
be upgraded at any point. You can use
two of these or three of these I think
or you can upgrade to their
generator X which is more of a powerful
machine.
But then you get so many packs of tens
pads that you can continue to use time
and time again and then when they get
worn out, you can obviously just replace
it with another one and then I think you
can actually buy these on the Spooky2
website as well.
Okay, so you get loads of tens pads so I
don't think you'll be running out of
those very quickly.
You also get a set of sunglasses that
are for the um
for the wristband that I will show you
very quickly now um that I think I've
shown you as well but the wristband is
what I've used and I haven't used the
tens pads so much but I should be
because they're more powerful than just
this alone.
Um but this is obviously like a um
an Apple Watch or a watch.
Um and they do also give you in this
pack um some Velcro
extenders.
So, basically you can put this anywhere
on your body, it just doesn't have to go
on your wrist. It can actually feed
through here. It can be a little bit
tricky for the start, okay, but it can
go through here and then obviously it
closes and then it gives you an extended
watch, okay?
And then this just literally sticks on
here and then you can have this on your
leg, okay, your upper or lower arm,
upper or lower leg, okay, mainly.
Obviously do not go above your neck or
on your neck, okay? Don't put it on your
temple or your eyes or anything like
that, right? Um
but that is another product that you get
with this beginners package, okay? This
is this is very good. It's it's good to
use with the tens pads, okay, as well.
So, the reason why I'm doing them
singular is because it started to look
very much of a mess when I was trying to
kind of review them because there's a
lot of wires and a lot of leads in here
but that is a good thing because this is
a very long tens pad lead that you get
with it as well. So, it'll help you be
able to move around and still continue
to work and not get things like jammed
and stuff so you get plenty of cable
um that you can use
for different kind of things that I will
show you in a bit because there is also
some tubes that you can use for a foot
spa in general, okay? But the general
rule of thumb is is that this
fits onto the generator and you turn
and it locks it into place,
okay? Straightforward, very quick, very
easy, okay? This end of the other end of
the cable,
basically there is a red and a black
cable that goes into the tens pads,
okay? And there you go, you've pretty
much set it up but Spooky2 clients and
everybody that's been working for
Spooky2 or been promoting them, I've
done multiple different videos that you
can find on their website and also on
their YouTube channel that will all be
linked below with also the code that you
can use to get 5% off, okay?
Okay, guys, so I really do apologize if
you start to see a few edits
within these segments but I really
wanted to give this
its credit where it's due, okay? And I
really wanted to make sure that I tested
the product enough so I kind of can
credit, you know, what I think about the
product itself.
Now, this is obviously you so you know
this channel that we do I do a lot of
remote viewing obviously, okay?
Spiritual remote viewing. Now this is
actually called the Spooky2 remote. So
if you look at this as your personal
twin flame or soulmate, so if we was to
actually look at twins, okay?
When a twin is born,
they always say that they can actually
feel and know exactly what is going to
happen when it happens. I know when
they're when they're feeling down, when
they're feeling happy, if they're about
to call, if there's something wrong with
my twin.
Spiritually and metaphysically a lot of
us kind of go through that with our
soulmates and twin flame on our journey,
right? We become empathic and there's a
metaphysical connection between the
person that actually isn't born as a
twin, but within spiritual entanglement
or quantum physics or metaphysics, we
feel the energy of people, but
especially like our you know, twin flame
or soulmate, right? So this is actually
called the spooky remote and I actually
do a lot of remote viewing. So why is
this really important? Okay, so when you
start to look at like if you're using
tens pads or if you're using the wrist
watch or the you know, all of the other
things that I've shown you,
you obviously have to be sitting down
and put the tens pads on or holding the
poles or putting them into a foot spa
and that is going to be like where
there's wires everywhere and I can't
really move around. How long do I have
to sit here? Every human being is very
impatient, especially if you're a
Sagittarius, maybe.
I'm just kidding. But like um, you know,
so what this is
is if you look at it as a personal Wi-Fi
connection between yourself and
yourself.
So let me hopefully explain. So inside
of this remote is a little white sticker
and inside of the white sticker is my
thumbnail.
Okay? So a thumbnail it you can either
use saliva or blood, but basically what
you want is your DNA.
Now because a thumbnail or a fingernail
takes the longest to actually die off,
okay? When it's separated from you, it
starts to die off, but it takes quite a
long time.
So really there is a molecular What do
they What do they call it? Like a
quantum entanglement? But a structure
that is still a part of you that is
still alive somewhere within the earth,
no matter where you are. And that's
where the the remote comes into into
play.
So you could look at it as like
um, a Wi-Fi signal between yourself,
wherever you are, if you're traveling,
if you're going to the shops, if you're
not at home, if you are walking around
your home, you don't have to be
connected via wires, you can be
connected by the
uh remote.
you take a
um, a piece of your DNA, you put it
inside of the remote, okay? And you fix
it to the spooky boost and then the
boost obviously
um,
goes on the generator,
okay? We lock it into place
and then when you do start the program,
you will see lights flashing at the
beginning here pretty much.
And what you would do is you would go on
to the program itself that I do show you
at the end and you look for uh remote
and then there is uh special programs to
go through. Now what I will say is they
ask you to go through a certain protocol
first that can take up to it's it's a
very long time. But when I had it
running myself, I was thinking, I have
to admit, I really don't know if this is
going to work.
But when I run the protocol,
I realized that when it came to the
metals in your teeth, like
um, I I forget what they call it within
your teeth, but it goes through metals
of your body to remove them and things
like that, my teeth started to feel like
uh sensitive and I could taste metal in
my mouth.
And this is not even connected to me via
a wire. It's just has my DNA in it. And
at the time I wasn't at home, I put it
on, I left it running and then I went to
the pub to see my friend. As I As I'm
sitting there, I'm kind of getting this
metallic taste in my mouth and feeling
like I've got a filling or something or
or whatnot. So I was like, what is that?
And I was like, oh my god, I can
remember now. This remote is actually
running at home while I'm not here. That
is so bizarre, okay? So it does go
through all of the things and it gives
you like a general clean out and and
everything and then it kind of replaces
everything and and stuff like that, but
generally, rule of thumb, that your DNA,
whatever in here, as long as it's still
be alive and you don't have to change
it, it still has a molecular
construction between you and whatever it
is that you've put in here. So it can
still pick up your DNA like it would
energetically of a twin flame, a
soulmate or an actual twin. It knows
where you are, what you're doing. It
knows all of your DNA.
And then it can send signals from your
DNA that is still connected to you and
tethered to you energetically.
Okay? It's It's absolutely marvelous
like because if you look at these this
machine here is pretty much what you
would be using 99% of the time because
the moment that you know that you can
use this and learn how to use it and
start to learn about energy and which we
already know on this channel,
that you'll realize that you can kind of
go about your day and do whatever you
like and you can set many a different
program
that you think, okay, this is like 8 or
9 hours program. I haven't got time in
order to sit around for 9 hours while
this program runs because I need to move
about, I need to get up, I need to
answer the door and stuff like that, go
to the toilet, right? So you can do
whatever you like here. So majority of
people that use the Spooky2 product,
they end up buying quite a lot of these
or they buy the generator X and they
have one and then they have another one
and another one and another one.
Now this don't just also heal yourself,
it can also heal anybody or any piece of
DNA that you've got inside it.
Now that doesn't even have to be human.
That can also be your cat or your dog or
your pets.
Okay? Say if you know that your dog or
your cat is suffering through cataracts
or it has pain elements and it has joint
elements and stuff and you really care
about your pet,
you can take a toenail clipping or a
claw clipping of your pet and put it
inside of here and run a structure
through here and see if you see any
changes within your animal.
Okay? Like I said, there are there are a
lot of things that you can also test if
you start to get into the scientific
parts of it. There was also a very
interesting subject that they brought up
as well
that like um,
what we call them in Britain is midgets,
midges, okay? And they come from the
corn when when it starts to become hot
and the corn is being grown, there are
these very small little flies that start
to circulate around Britain and it
becomes very annoying because they're so
small, but they just land on you and
it's oh
and they're everywhere around the
houses. So
you can run these certain things that
give off frequencies that actually deter
them from coming around your house,
haha,
right? So if you're
or an ant infestation and whatnot and
you use it on that, it will actually
stop all those creatures from coming and
circulating around your house cuz it's
giving off this frequency that, you
know, like um, a repellent if you like,
okay?
So very interesting facts that you can
learn about this. So just very briefly
before I move on to the next product,
this is the spooky remote
and it's like remote viewing in a way,
okay? It can pick up things
like it can pick up from you to here and
heal you at a distance and it can either
kill off certain pathogens or it can
heal them or do both. But all of the
things that you can do mainly with the
tens pads and everything, you can also
do very much so with this. It's your
personal twin flame soulmate, okay? So
now we're going to go on to the next
product.
Now the next product as well is also
very fascinating
for one of the other little things that
they've got that is so simple when you
know what it does. So basically it's the
spooky pulse.
Now you can also buy
um, in another package or separately on
its own and you can use the product code
below if you have one of these machines
and you just want to get one of the
products individually.
But this is the Spooky2 pulse.
So basically how this works
is is that you plug this directly into
your PC, okay? Your laptop or your
computer, but it really needs to be a
direct feed.
Okay? It doesn't really need to be in a
in a USB extension,
it needs to go directly into the main
USB port of your computer. Okay, because
it's reading pulse.
And because it reads your pulse, it
doesn't need any kind of delay. So,
there shouldn't really be a delay. It
has to be the shortest amount of lead
that there is like this, the shortest
amount of distance between here and
this, and then it will start to pick up
your pulse rate when you obviously like
use this part.
Now, this has sensors inside, obviously,
like a finger pulse monitor would do.
But, do if you do have this, do not have
it on your fingernail.
Okay, needs to be on your actual skin.
Okay?
So, when that's running, this can run
um Now, that you do have to sit down for
this one, and I and I must say that I
haven't been able to sit around long
enough cuz I have ADHD, and I'm a very
busy person. So, I I I wasn't able to
sit around for the 15 to probably 20
minutes that this will take to run, but
I will do.
But, as far as it works, it basically
takes your pulse, and then it runs what
the Spooky2 software
like if if there's something wrong with
you, it it it sweeps your body and it
says, "Okay, your body will adapt better
to these kind of frequencies."
Now, as far as I know, don't quote me on
it, but they do also have that is
something very similar to this,
but they're two uh individual little
plates. And you can put the DNA inside
of the plate, and you can run a
protocol, and it will pretty much pick
up all of the DNA and everything that
goes through your body, your heart rate,
and all that sort of stuff, and it will
kind of pinpoint what you need work on,
and then probably
advise you on the programs that it
thinks that you'd benefit more, or it
does things like it would um alter the
the frequency to your specific body
type. Cuz we we all have different body
types, and it is
this is no wonder drug or anything,
okay? It will take practice because
everybody's body DNA is different,
constructed differently than everybody.
There's barely anybody that's exactly
the same. So, each machine really needs
to be tailored towards what works for
you and what may not work for you. And
if it doesn't work, it's probably
because the frequencies need to be more
in tune. And these are the ways that you
can hopefully give the machine a little
bit of more information about yourself.
Okay?
Cuz don't forget like the Spooky Remote,
it needs to have DNA that is yourself to
give you signals about yourself.
Right? This is pretty much the same.
When the computer and the program starts
to know more about you, it can give you
the better program. It's pretty It's a
lot like the Matrix in a way. It'll re-
re- redesign all of your numerology and
your molecular construction of your DNA,
and then run run through your body as a
sweep to think, "Okay, we really need to
send these numbers into this body
because that'll work
a lot better, right?" So, it works off
um
frequencies and so on and so forth. But,
very interesting to be able to sit long
enough to be able to think, "I need the
computer to know more about me." This is
the way I do it. And then when it knows
my heart rate and everything else, it
will know what programs fit better for
me. Okay?
So, sorry if I had to um if I've been if
you you probably won't see it, but I've
edited it the best I can because I
wanted to make sure that I'd kind of
tested these and realized what may or
may not kind of work.
I will give you a little bit um I left
this on for my
uh I really can't remember what it's
called. It's like
Obscemia or something. But, because I
spend a long time sitting up,
okay, I get all of my legs and my feet
swell a lot because my my my legs are
not equal with my heart for the fluid to
run, you know, in and out of my heart.
So, I I get swollen legs and ankles and
feet.
Um
when I was using this, I may or may not
have been using the right
kind of frequency, or I hadn't used this
in order for it to know what to use.
It didn't really work so well. But, when
I was using the actual TENS pads, it did
work, okay? So, there's a fine line
between this knowing you and whether
it's going to like what it's going to
work on. Well, I would say that these
are better more for the the energy
clearing and the energy healing and the
frequencies and stuff that run through
your body more so than what I would say
of a like a swelling of the legs and the
ankles and so on and so forth. I would
say this is more energy type sort of
clearing and and healing and stuff like
that than I would say the you know, the
fixing of of a swollen leg or ankle.
But, I haven't tested it long enough.
But, what I can say is that the TENS
pads helped with that element a lot more
than what this one did. When I was
running the spiritual bar kind of
cleansing program that I put together
for myself, which was what you will see
is the um Kundalini experience, the
seven chakras, the balancing the energy
in, energy out, the aura, the negative
thinking program. When I run that, I
felt like all kinds of peculiar.
So, I could really feel that it was
doing something. And for that brief hour
or so, I felt fantastic. Like I really
did feel good. And I was I wasn't at
home.
Like I said, I was out visiting a
friend.
We were catching up. I left it running
on the spiritual program that I've made
for myself. Left it running, and I'm in
a fast
energetic mood of I was speaking
clearly. We had great communication
between me and my friend.
It It was just and I and I was talking
to him about it, and he likes a lot of
these sort of things.
And he was kind of like, "Well, you
know, there's there's definitely a
structure between it." And we were
having like our a little conversation.
But,
I would definitely say that this works
for the majority of things, but on other
things, there may need to be a few
tweaks and twists that you may need to
to look at, okay?
That's where using this or the plates
that you can get from Spooky2,
and then like I said, you can use this
for yourself. Later on, you can probably
buy another one if you could afford it.
And you can use one for your mom, one
for your dad or your parents, your
siblings, your animals, your son, your
daughter, your friend. And you could
very much do this kind of thing for a
living as well.
You can do people from overseas and
whatnot, right? You uh get their DNA, so
on and so forth. And you run all of
these different protocols at different
different times, okay? So, you write
down on it whose DNA it is, when you got
it, how long it will last, 3 months,
started it, you know, blah blah blah.
So, there you go. So, we'll go on to the
next segment.
I've been using this.
So, this is for you guys that may
experience a lot of things that I do. I
can't breathe through my nose.
I had polyps, and I had uh loads of
problems with my nose when I was
younger, and believe it or not,
uh a lot of you possibly don't know that
I can't smell. I've never had a sense of
smell.
If I smell like perfume very close to
the bottle, I possibly can smell it a
little bit, but I generally can't really
smell anything.
Now, I've always got a blocked nose,
okay? And I probably talk that way, and
sometimes you can possibly hear that.
And I have to use a lot of these,
antihistamines. So, I've been using them
for a very very very long time since I
was probably 5 years old. Okay? So, what
this does is hopefully going to replace
any drug or any kind of antihistamine
that you may have for like headaches or
nasal congestion or guitar or anything
like that for cold, flu. You can
obviously have your TENS pads running,
and you can also have these running at
the same time.
Okay? Now, in the box that you also do
get
is um a pack of
uh
I don't know. I think they're kind of
like covers, and it also makes sure that
it sticks in your nose or your ear.
I think you can also put them in your
mouth as well, okay? For like teeth ache
and tooth ache.
But, these just generally it's the same
as everything that you'll find with
their products. It's all quite
straightforward. You know, you just plug
one end into the generator, okay? Or
into the boost port.
Okay? Literally like so.
And you'll see the program part after
this section. And then these light up,
and there's like rays of light inside of
here. And it kind of gives off a very
warm
uh light like the watch does, okay? And
these are either in your
ears or your nose, and I think maybe
sometimes your mouth. Not really sure.
Make sure you wipe them before you put
them in from your ears or your nose to
your mouth, obviously, okay? But,
there's another product that you get
that is enabling you to be able to
think, "Okay, where
is the pain or where is it that needs
work?" Because guarantee you within this
pack that you get from them, it provides
you with upper and middle and lower
body, okay, that you can use, okay? So,
there's another product that you
actually get. So, there is the unboxing
and we're going to go over to the the
bit that's difficult, but it's not very
difficult, but you will see that I also
make a mistake.
But, I've put together a spiritual kind
of healing cleansing bath, if you like,
and I'm showing you how to use their
program that you also get free of charge
that you can download from their website
and use all of these products with. And
I'm kind of showing you how to
how I put together a chakra and aura
healing Kundalini
energy healing in and L negative
thinking, negative thoughts, and all of
that is on the next section. But, what I
will say to you is that if you click any
of the links provided below, you will
find a discount code or somewhere of
getting a discount that you can use in
order to purchase a whole package
or individual items. If you've already
got the Spooky2 stuff, you can, you
know, buy something with 5% off.
Um
I do receive a very small commission in
order for you to do so, which is very
helpful. So, please make sure that you
use that link and that code so I can
also get a very small commission. But, I
just would like to say thank you for
Spooky2 for sending me this product and
putting me onto something new that I
didn't actually know myself that has
really been helping me on my journey and
to be able to um
help with my remote viewing and my
visions that I receive. This is a very
big um best friend of mine at the
moment. So, I'm going to leave you and
let you go over to me and um I would
just like to say thank you and I will
see you soon. Okay, guys, so here we are
in the Spooky2 software and I will admit
to you that there is a slight amount of
um learning curve. It can it I mean, it
depends on if you're really good, if
you're technical minded and stuff, and I
don't really think that you need to be
that technical minded. What I will say
is though is is that you do have to
obviously have a laptop or a PC
uh because this uses Windows.
Um and I I don't think that you can use
an iPad
um or a an Android. I'm really not sure,
but I will have to ask the guys
um over at Spooky2, but as far as I
know, really you've got to have a PC or
a laptop. But, most people do these
days.
Um anyway, so you're going to be seeing
my screen here. So,
as all of us that are on this channel
are spiritual or a lot of people that
use these kind of things are very
spiritual in mind because they use
frequencies, vibrations, and obviously
when we do meditation and stuff like
that, we look at like chakra healing,
auras, uh vitality of life energy,
energy healing,
uh what we feel through soulmates and
stuff and connections with soulmates and
people and stuff like that. So, this
machine kind of does it for you. It's
like your own personal soulmate, if you
like. So, what I've actually discovered
this morning as myself is that you can
make up a program and I will run you
through this, but you can make up a
program yourself of something that you
want running
of like your morning ritual.
So,
for a lot of us, we obviously do a lot
of meditations in the mornings before we
start our practice or stuff like that
and whatever it is that we're doing.
So, we can make up a program that is
going to allow us in order to more than
likely meditate at the same time, but
then also use the Spooky2 products that
also give us a very big boost and
enhanced energy feeling at the same time
as listening to meditation.
Now, Spooky2 actually do do their uh own
meditation music that is well, to be
fair, a lot of it is not actually music,
it's frequencies. So, you probably can't
hear it. Uh it's a little bit like a dog
whistle or a deer whistle.
If you know my my uh last prediction of
where I actually predicted my own
accident, then uh oh dear. Huh, but
never mind. Let's kind of go into the
program here. So, what you'll see that
I've done, if you have a quick look
here,
it says aura and then it also says
emotional spectrum.
Energy in,
energy vitalize one, vitality,
energy vitalize capital, whatever that
is, I'm not sure. Uh fat energy
metabolism. So, it's kind of like
digesting all of the fat cells, kind of
going through your body, organizing
everything that is to do with like food
and things like this, okay? And then
keeping the good stuff and trying to get
rid of the bad stuff. So, it'll be like
cholesterol and things you can kind of
look into.
Um
but like and then also fatigue syndrome.
So, feeling very tired and energetically
drained throughout the day is obviously
going to be a big one for a lot of us.
And then also I've got a Kundalini
expand.
Okay. Now, this is just something that
I've made up very quickly that I thought
a lot of you guys would be very
interested in.
So, here in this box here,
okay? If I can bring up um a pen,
you'll be able to see what I'm kind of
doing here. Okay, here. You'll be able
to see that there are frequencies,
certain frequencies that are kind of
telling you all of the information that
you're going to be able to see
everywhere, okay?
So, it goes through its cycle,
okay, blah blah blah.
Let me just kind of get rid of this. I'm
sort of multitasking here.
And I'm also very new to this myself.
You know me, I'm always blatantly honest
with what I do. I've had They've been
absolutely great over uh in Spooky2 um
with all of their communication
that they've done in order to help me.
But, let's see anyway.
So, for a start, what I've done is I've
started off with a
Let me try and figure out how to work.
So, preset. So, we go back to presets,
okay? So, what we're looking at, these
are there's healing or there's At the
moment, that we're just going to stick
with the basics cuz a lot of these can,
you know, it can really start to get
very difficult for you me to overwhelm
you and that is not my goal.
So, we're looking at either healing or
killing.
But, the moment that you tap on these,
it will give you a
um a brief disc uh description or a note
of what shell presets mean.
Okay.
Basically, a shell is something that's
empty.
Okay, it's like an empty shell and it's
ready to be filled with something. And
that's all of the information and stuff
that you can use in order to fill it
with all of your own programs and
frequencies, pretty much, okay, in a
nutshell.
Um
So, what we're looking at is when we use
these here, that is home, obviously,
okay? And this goes up a level back to
the last page or we can just go home.
Okay. So, really what we're looking at
is we're looking at that we want to do
some
we want a a shell preset, okay?
That means an empty page, blank page,
basically. Then we're looking at coil,
contact, plasma, remote, scalar,
footbath, uh general, spooky audio,
which is the is kind of like silent
meditation, but only frequency-wise that
you're more than likely not going to be
able to hear,
or spooky cold laser.
Now, all of this will be put in the
description box below of what these
mean, okay, and what they are, and I
will probably go over a lot of that sort
of stuff.
Um well, I'm recording this first, so
it's probably I've already showed you,
maybe.
So, we're going to pick contact.
So, contact is obviously things that are
contacting your skin.
Okay, like we'll just use, say, the tens
pads, maybe the poles.
Um I would also say that the cold laser
is the wristband, but it is also
contacting your skin, so it's kind of
both. You can use like tens pads and the
wristbands and the watches kind of
products that they have on offer and
that you will also get with
your purchase, if you purchase anything
really. But, if you purchase the kit,
the starter kit, you'll kind of get
everything in you know, that you need.
So, what we're looking at now is we're
going to look at healing,
So, when I double click healing or just
click healing, it'll give us a brief
description of that this shell preset uh
preset uh contains no frequencies. It
has been designed for programs that heal
um
entrain or detox.
Okay.
So, we're looking at healing. So, then
what we do is we go over to
programs,
okay, and we want to fill this shell
that we've got, which is loaded
programs, into the shell. So, we're
going to load the shell full of
programs.
So, what you'll see is that I typed here
is energy cuz that's really what this
channel will deal with mainly, I would
say.
Okay. So, we're looking at adrenal gland
balance, adrenal glands. Then you've got
cuz there are so many programs on here.
So, aura sounds good, right? So, aura
excuse me, will give us a brief
description of what aura is. An aura of
human energy field is, according to
New Age beliefs a colored Uh well, I'm
not going to read it all out, but it
kind of goes over it for you there.
Okay. So, we're going to have aura. So,
you can either double click aura or you
can press this button here.
Plus. So, it's added aura into our shell
of a practice that we're going to be
using in the morning times or in the
evening or at night, but say we're doing
it in the morning before we start our
our journey of life, basically.
Especially if you are tarot card readers
or you experience a lot of
karma and bad thoughts because there's
another one on here that we'd like to
add, which is also negative thinking.
So, you will also see here that there is
a timeline of how long these will take.
So, to do a aura sweep it says that it
will take up to 3 minutes in order to do
it. So, that's really not long. So, that
is good for our starting off point of
uh frequencies looking at our aura.
Okay. So, then we can kind of go down
the list here. Blood pressure.
So, if we have high blood pressure, we
can kind of think, you know what, I've
got headache and so on and so forth. And
blood pressure really could be causing a
lot of blocks, clearing emotional trauma
and balance. So, it can be like PTSD and
stuff. It's really interesting to read
what it is that they've put that they
do. So, I'm liking a bit of that. So,
we're going to have a bit of blood
pressure and balance, too. Okay.
So, um then we're looking at cerebral
energy. So, that's like the cerebral
cortex. Okay.
A program called by uh Van
uh Gelder Gelder, I don't know. Energy.
Can't read, but spirit did give me a
gift. I can read from the Akashic
records and I can read people and tarot
cards and speak to the deceased. I just
can't read words. Unfortunately, not
very well.
So, we're looking at cerebral energy.
Another energy another time of 3
minutes.
So, we're going to add that into our
shell, as well.
Then we're looking at chronic fatigue
syndrome.
So, if you are like me and you
experience things like sleep apnea this
is very good for sleep apnea because
you'll know that during the day
through not really having REM sleep,
your brain is going to be causing a lot
of confusion
and a lot of fatigue. And we really want
good energy around us and we want to be
um
Sorry, my phone is also going off. I've
got a lot of clients.
But we want like really good clear
crystal thoughts. Okay. So, we're going
to have um fatigue.
Okay. Then we've got emotional spectrum.
We start going on from energy, they
start to give us this these um presets
that are also relating to energy of
emotional spectrum.
Right? So, the emotional spectrum is an
energy field that is um
fluid by the emotions for uh
fueled by the emotions of all sentient
beings mind. So, this is a very
spiritual kind of
program or exercise that
I'm going to start doing and adding into
my daily routine.
So, we're going to add emotional
spectrum.
Then we're also got another one, which
is like uh energy flow.
So, if I didn't say the other one that
we just looked at, emotional spectrum,
that is also a 3-minute. So, we're
really not looking at long. So, energy
flow, 9 minutes. Okay.
So, we'll we'll add a bit of that, too.
That's obvious, right? Energy flow.
That's 9 minutes. Then you've got
looking at energy in and also energy
out.
So, I think they're probably both good
to go with those. So, we'll have energy
in and energy out.
Okay.
Then we're looking at energy vitalized.
Now, I know that I added this
to my preset, this vitalized energy.
Um vitality. And I really did feel that
this morning
um after about an hour and a half of me
waking up, I'm kind of thinking, right,
I need to start doing my readings and
start doing YouTube. Obviously feeling
very drained throughout the night
because of sleep apnea. So, energy
vitalization for me is very important.
So, I'm kind of like, okay, I really
want to add a bit of this
energy vitalized one.
Uh it also says depression in general.
Now, the first one doesn't really says
say that. This one goes more onto foods
that will help you energize your body uh
batteries and help you recover
um and revitalize when you feel tired.
So, it's kind of like giving you
vitamins cuz you can actually have
minerals and vitamins, as well through a
lot of the programs that they've got,
but this is kind of like an added bonus.
So, we want the we really want the
vitalized one.
For me, not really vitalized two. Okay.
Um then we can go on to another one, but
we're just going to kind of stick with
the first one. Okay.
Did I add it? Don't think I did.
Um vitalized one. Yeah, I did. Yeah. So,
we can double click that one and that
will go.
So, energy delivering.
Okay, not really a description in that
one, but we've got a lot of energy still
kind of stuff going on, but I am going
to add that one.
So, essential oils
fat cells
Okay. Now, this is all just under the
energy of
the category of energy.
So, um
fats energy metabolism
fatigue two three fatigue general,
fatigue syndrome chronic fatigue and
another one. These are all been altered
to different frequencies and times, but
you will have to read these kind of
things to like drowsiness. Okay.
Gives you a description of what fatigue
is and chronic fatigue and so on and so
forth. So, we're going to look I'm going
to look at syndrome. Okay.
So, we're going to add that.
Then we've got intensities.
Um gastrointestinal tract um digestive
tract.
So, gut the GI tract.
Um we'll add that, too. Okay. Now,
Kundalini, there we go. So, this is one
that I also found out this morning by
basically just browsing through a lot of
these programs. Is is that so cuz I was
going to put in spiritual in the box
here to try and
you know, break down because there are
so many different programs that it would
take you hours in order to go through
them all. So, they've obviously given us
a window like Google is, like you kind
of do your own little search and it will
come up with all of the things that
you're kind of looking for.
I happened to put in energy. So,
Kundalini expand. In yoga
uh female energy
uh blah blah blah blah blah so on and so
forth. So, we're going to have
Kundalini. Now, you've got minerals
minerals again
muscle toxic
uh plant
vitalized energy, vital energy
uh ATP
uh there are so many on here, guys. I
don't want to bore you. I thought that
said Akashic records then for the
moment.
Um
What have we got? Calcium
uh copper
So, it's looking at all of the
uh metals within our blood, as well.
Um
detoxing
I'm trying to think what else we could
kind of add to our morning routine of
spiritual enlightenment
here.
Um but I'm sure they are all here.
Magnesium, I would say that's a very
good one in order to look at cuz we're
not looking at
killing, don't forget. We're looking at
healing.
Cuz you can have programs, obviously,
running that are doing a sweep over your
body to kill off certain organisms and
things that are in your body.
Okay. And then we're also looking at
then rebuilding the structure of the
body.
Okay. And then putting in fresh amounts
of like magnesium. Okay. So, you can do
different sweeps, different settings.
Say one set for killing and destroying
and searching and destroying. And then
we can one have another setting of like
um
vitalization and to replace all of the
bad with the good.
So, magnesium would also be a very good
one, I would say, because a lot of
people could be deficient in magnesium,
especially when we start to look around
the uh context of like sleeping and
fatigue and late nights and stuff like
that. Magnesium for me is a very good
one. So, we'll add a bit of magnesium to
it. Okay.
So, I'm going to leave that at the
moment there. And then what we're going
to do is we're we're to go over to
settings. Now, I really don't want to
confuse you on here because I'm still
learning myself. But, what I do like to
do is I look at this part of wobble.
Okay, which is amplitude and frequency
and harmonic wobble.
Okay. So, if you are into music like I
am and I mix and master my own music as
well.
If you was to ever make your If you've
ever made a piece a track and a piece of
um meditation music
or music in general general, we know
that when we look at waveform, we start
to look at these curves and bends,
square waves where it'd be like
And that's obviously how we make tone
and tone of voice and music and
frequencies and why some people's voices
annoying and why some people's voice are
very settling and relaxing. Tone of
voice, so it's frequencies, right? So,
waveform. So,
when the waveform is going through your
system,
we like to make sure that it heals or
kills everything.
So, we start to look at Okay, I want a
sawtooth.
Okay.
As an amp wobble, so it wobbles a little
bit. And then we also want to say have
an inverted sawtooth as well.
But, I will kind of go over this and
then feathering harmonic give it a
feather edge. Okay. It's basically just
making sure that
you don't miss any kind of things that
are in your body that it misses and it
skips over
or skips a beat or skips a wave and it
jumps over it and it escapes through the
body. We want to make sure it does like
a really good sweep all the way through
the body.
So, we'll kind of leave that at the
moment, but then we'll go to control.
Okay. So, I'm up here if you can see my
uh cursor here.
So, this is also very important. So,
what we're looking at in this general
box here where it says generator three,
healing, is all of these numbers and
these are representing like the
frequencies and everything that we've
been given through all of these things.
So, we're looking at the emotional
spectrum as well We've got the aura,
emotional spectrum, energy in, energy
vitalize one of vitality one and two,
fat energy metabolism,
uh fatigue syndrome and kundalini
expand.
Okay. These are all the frequencies that
it's going to do.
Okay.
So,
what we do is that is we have to make
sure that we press
override generator.
Okay. And then we press
this is the generator.
And it gives us all of these. Okay. It
starts again.
Okay.
Then, what we can do is we press
start.
And what you will hear, if you did hear
that,
is a your um
channel generator that you've got, your
little box with your dials on it, and
your watch or your tens pads that are
connected to it, you will hear it click
just very slightly and that means that
everything all of this information
and all of these things that we've put
in here
will go into the little box that we've
got on our desk and then you will see if
you've got the the wrist strap,
okay, or the cold laser,
you will see that there is a
you'll know that it's on because
the lights will come on and you'll know,
okay, it's 100% working.
Okay.
Um so, that's just a very quick general
overview of me putting together a very
quick
um
daily routine of what I would do. And
now, if I was to save this, which I will
show you in a moment,
if I was to save this, obviously I would
save it on my computer as a PDF file or
a new file of spiritual vital
vitalization morning routine. And then
when I come to user guide
and I think, okay, in the morning I want
to do my spiritual stuff, that's where
I'm going to look in my user um user
presets.
Okay. And here look, user preset. So,
we've used the shell and then we'd go on
to user presets and look to see what
we've got.
We'll look at biofeedback in a second.
Okay.
Okay, guys. So, what I did want to very
quickly show you as well is mistakes
that you can make uh and they but but it
like I said, when you're using this
program, it's a learning curve and they
are quite easily overcome. So, what I've
realized by what we was just doing by
adding all of these presets and the
energy vitalize and we've made a program
and an empty shell. Okay. When I'd gone
to control to press override and start,
nothing happened on the cold laser here.
Okay. So, what I've realized is is that
I need the booster.
So, the booster would have been
something that I would have shown you at
the beginning of what that is and what
that can do, but this wasn't working and
I knew because the lights hadn't come on
on the back.
So, I thought, okay, it may need the
booster. So, you may need in order to do
quite a bit research, but over on the
Spooky2 website and also over on their
YouTube channel, they have loads of
different videos of different people
kind of showing you how to do certain
things. But, what I wanted to just very
quickly to show you is I'm not going to
show it in the camera cuz it might blind
you
cuz you also get some um
sunglasses that come with this. But,
what it kind of looks like. So, we're
now kind of got our presets. We know
what we're doing. Okay. We're looking at
the cold laser, which is down here.
Okay. We've got all our programs,
kundalini. I will also state that you
can organize all of these here to what
you want to for the Spooky2 generator to
do first.
So, if I wanted my blood pressure one
doing first, I would hit the arrow with
a line on the top and it would go
directly to the top.
Okay. Or if I hit the bottom arrow, it'd
go directly to the bottom and it
reorganize all of these. Okay.
So, we've kind of got our programs, blah
blah blah. We go over to the control
panel. We hit override generator.
Then we hit the
generator three and then we hit start.
You'll hear a click
and then I can see it glowing from the
bottom of the table that you will see
that this is now glowing. I don't want
to shoot glare it into the camera, but
you will see that it is glowing.
Okay. And that means that you'll know
that this is actually working. Now, what
they do give you with this
is obviously it's like a watch and you
can put
um obviously this on your wrist, but
they do also give you a um an extended
band that you can kind of
um
put on here. Okay. And then you connect
these two together
and then these two together here and
then you can end up putting it around
your leg or your ankle
um or further up your arm. Okay. And it
gives you it makes this bigger, so you
can actually wrap it around somewhere
else on your body other than your wrist.
So, what I would do obviously I would
have this done before I hit start,
but I would have this on my wrist here.
I know that it's going cuz I can kind of
peek through there and see that it's
running. Okay. And then what we are
running obviously is the kundalini
expand, the aura, emotional spectrum,
vitalizer of energy. When it gets to the
energy ones, I can really feel those. I
haven't tried the kundalini one yet um
and some of these other ones I haven't
tried yet.
But, you can also Don't quote me on
this, but I'm sure you can as well.
You can connect up the tens pads.
But, I would have shown you this video
what you get with this product at the
beginning. But, you would connect your
tens pads
um
outlet like this cable, but the other
one, to here. Okay. And that would also
give you double the boost, so you can
have your wrist going and then you can
also have the tens pads.
So, what it normally would be, okay,
I'll have this on my left wrist, okay,
on my right wrist, and then I'll have a
tens pad on my ankle on the opposite
side of my body, so it creates a flow
from left to right.
Okay. I might end up doing another video
about placements of certain things
because
obviously it's the conducted of energy
like you would use a tens pad or a tens
machine, but you don't normally feel
these. Okay.
Um some some of them you do. You can
actually feel it working, but it is not
like a tens machine where you put it on
and you're you're getting jolts of
electricity that's kind of
trying to you know, um
what was I saying? Um your joints and
muscles.
When you use a tens pad, it volts your
muscle in order to try and release the
tendons to stop back ache and pain.
This isn't the same thing. It's
frequency. Okay. So, a lot of the time
you may not feel the fact that it's
working, but then sometimes you can
think, oh my god, I'm really starting to
feel different and and stuff like that
straight away. Okay. But, you just can't
feel it on your body actually working.
You know what I'm saying?
Okay. So, I know that that is because
the light is actually functioning on the
wrist and I know now that it is cycling
through all of these and it will take up
to 57 minutes.
Now, I did change these because like I
said, I did get into a bit of a
I clicked it and the wrist wasn't what
wasn't working. So, I thought, "Okay, I
need to debunk why this isn't working."
The only reason it wasn't is because I
didn't have
the booster attached to the generator.
Okay? Cuz it is a lot of energy that it
needs to boost. So, I needed this on.
Okay? So, I wanted to show you that
working and there's that segment.
So, that is my conclusion of the product
of Spooky2. All links are provided
below. I will receive a very small
amount of
money
if you guys use my link. So, I really
would appreciate it if you did buy it
from my link or from definitely the code
that I may be there. How I'm not 100%
sure what is going to be there yet cuz
I'm recording this ahead of time of me
actually knowing, but it will be in the
description by the time this is posted.
If you do want to buy something, I'm
just letting you know that I will
receive a small commission for you guys
buying it. And then, if you do, I would
like to hear from you. Let me know, how
has it been working for you? I may do a
collaboration video with you and put
your testimony on here or or whatnot and
see what your benefits that you've had
from it. Okay?
So, all links are provided below. Thank
you so much again for Spooky2 allowing
me to demonstrate their product. I will
100% and have been using this every day
myself and I will be using it from now
on.
All links are provided below and thank
you very much. I really appreciate it
and I will see you guys very soon.